[Music] Are
you disappointed with your Diwali bonus?
I have something special for you.
Yes, friends, my name is Pramod Saraswat, and
I've been working in the financial industry for the past 17 years,
providing these services to over 2,500 satisfied customers. So, today I've
brought you a gift that will
provide security for your family.
For that, you'll have to promise me to stay
until the end of the video. If you stay
until the end, you'll take not one, but two
gifts from me. So, let's move on
to the plan. The plan is the
Salary Turn Plan from Aditya Billa Sunlife Insurance Company.
Approximately 2,100
companies have been identified and selected.
Employees of those 2,100 companies can avail this plan. So,
what's special about this plan is that you don't need to undergo
any medical checkup for up to a crore (10 million) sum. The
policy will be issued within one or two days, and a maximum of three days. The
second special feature for you is the first year of this plan.  On a
premium of Rs. 1000, if you are male then you
get a premium discount of Rs. 100 and if you
are female then you get a discount of Rs. 90 on the first year's premium.
I have mentioned this discount in case of non-smokers.
Whoever is a non-smoker, there is limited area liability for you. Along with this, let
us
understand this plan with some examples in which I have taken two
examples. One person is male whose age is
25 years and he takes this plan for the next 35 years
i.e. 35 plus 25, total his
age will be 60 years till his grave,
so for 60 years onwards, he will have to pay a
premium of Rs.
9558 for the second year.
Similarly, I am talking about the second condition, the
person whose age is 35 years and he
is a non-smoker because here we are talking about non-smokers, so if he
is a non-smoker and
he is 35 years old, he takes a plan for 25 years and
he has to pay the premium.
14414 Yes, you heard it absolutely right
14514 Both these premiums have been calculated on the second year on
words because
in this you get a discount on the first year's PM,
in this condition this plan is made for you, the
P will be different for both male and female, so first of all the
entry age in this is 55 years, that is, you can
take this plan till the last entry of 55 years
and coverage
can be taken up to 70 years, cover of Rs 50 lakh to Rs 1 crore will be available for
you without medical, if
you take more than Rs 1 crore then
both financial and medical conditions will be looked into in it but discount will be absolutely
for you, secondly along with this as
I told you that 2100 companies have been selected, it is
possible that in future more
companies may be added in it and till the age on date which I am
talking to you today, approximately
2100 companies have been included in it
and this special benefit is being given to the employees of those 2100 companies,
friends, did you  If you like this video,
I request you to
like it, subscribe to it and
forward it to your near and dear ones because
you never know for whom you might do something that can
change their life. It is possible that
this video may help some such brother or sister through
your forward message and bring
some change in their life. Thank you
[Music]
friends.